import { Question } from '../../model/question';

export const INFINITIVES_AND_GERUNDS: Question[] = [
  {question: 'Then you agree (give) it a try.' , response: 'to give'},
  {question: 'He denied (commit) the crime.', response: 'committing'},
  {question: 'Rather, I aim (show) that the world will be what we make it to be.', response: 'to show'},
  {question: 'He stopped when he saw her begin (shudder)', response: 'to shudder'},
  {question: 'The doctor says you can come home Friday if you continue (improve).', response: 'to improve'},
  {question: 'Ireland doesn\'t allow (smoke) in bars', response: 'smoking'},
  {question: 'Don\'t dare (say) it was her fault.', response: 'to say'},
  {question: 'The doctor generally advised (drink) low-fat milk.', response: 'drinking'},
  {question: 'She felt hurt, knowing she didn\'t deserve (feel) upset at him after doing the same thing.', response: 'to feel'},
  {question: 'He avoided (talk) to her.', response: 'talking'},
];
